Yor's other identity...
Thorn Princess.
You will be providing
protection on this mission.
Yor ended up on a luxury
cruise to help a member
of the mafia defect while
acting as her bodyguard.
Meanwhile...
We have a winner!
Anya won first place in a raffle,
and the Forgers just happened to
end up on the same cruise ship.
Many assassins had already snuck aboard.
Sickle-and-Chain Barnaby?!
What should I do? This is going
to turn into a commotion!
The lady from the circus is so cool!
Nice, Miss Anya!
Anya did her best to make sure Loid
didn't find out Yor's true identity.
Hero Anya cannot contain her excitement
from this epic adventure!
Could you be any lamer?
Yor continued to evade the enemy's attacks.
What am I doing this for?
I've found you.
While the fireworks show was happening,
Yor and the other assassins
were fighting to the death.
I just wanted to protect his simple life.
Things are not going to change.
No... Now more than ever...
I'm sure Loid will acknowledge me.
He'll forgive me.
I will not give up...
this fight!
The Hand That Connects to the Future
The fireworks were so pretty!
I'm glad you enjoyed them.
But I'm sorry we couldn't find Yor.
This ship is just too big.
Shock!
I'd totally forgotten about Mama!
I need to find her, quick!
The State Security Service
officers seem uneasy.
What's going on?
"Gather personnel quickly..."
"...has been set in a room..."
A bomb at the bottom of the ship?!
Say what now?!
But who set it? And why?
What should I do? Gather more information?
No... The State Security Service
officers will take care of this.
There'll definitely be risks
if I stick my neck out.
But the unthinkable could happen.
Considering the greater risk at hand,
I can't just avoid this, either.
But I also can't leave Anya alone.
What should I do?
Papa!
Anya's not done playing yet!
Hey...
Seriously? Right now?
Anya's gonna go play in there.
You go back to our room!
A daycare center? Perfect timing.
All right. I'll come get you in a bit,
then. Just stay right here.
Okee.
Please take good care of my daughter.
Her name is Anya.
Of course!
Wow, I get to play with a ball!
Okay, now's my chance.
All right, then.
What should we play with, Anya?
Anya is playing with this ball.
Yes, you sure are. You're amazing!
Gonna be bored with it soon, though.
And I'm bored.
Right... I guess that's enough of that.
Anya's gonna draw now.
Sure.
Just one second.
Okay, what should we draw?
Er... huh?
Anya?
Well? Can you disarm it?
Shut up. I'm trying to concentrate.
We're counting on you. There are some
really important people on this ship.
Just shut up already!
I heard there was a bomb in this area.
Oh... It's right over there.
Pardon.
I used to be in the navy. I was
in charge of disarming bombs.
I'd like to offer my assistance.
Is it possible to move
this bomb away from here?
It's not. There's a trap in it.
A time bomb, type B-CP62.
A bomb that extremists
from the West love using.
Is the suspect someone
important from the East?
Were they after this ship as a whole or...
No, I haven't heard anything from
HQ about a group like that.
It's possible the bomb was designed
to look like the West was responsible.
Hey, what's the matter?
Think you can deal with it?
No problem at all.
I'm going to leave the bomb
to Papa and find Mama.
Where are you?
To think she pretty much slaughtered
all those well-known assassins.
What a terrifying woman.
A bad guy's voice!
It's definitely time for me to go.
I've made more than enough from this job.
I'm getting the hell outta here
before those hyenas sniff me out.
You guys can keep playing around
for whatever time is left.
The front of the ship?
Soon, this whole ship is
gonna sink into the sea.
Though no one will know what
happened until it's far too late.
I lost the bad guy!
Well, whatever. Right now,
I need to find Mama.
The roof toward the front!
That's... Mama's stabby thing!
I'm too far!
I can't get close enough
to him to finish him off!
Mama's up there!
She's having trouble because
she's missing a weapon?!
She's too far away to hear clearly.
I need somewhere to climb up...
I can't find any!
Anya's gonna save Mama!
Reach her!
Rising Hope!
Hey! Stop making noise!
It wasn't me. What the hell was that sound?
If that demon woman finds
us, we're finished!
I know that. Our only chance is right now
as she's struggling with the katana guy.
This is our chance to take
out Gretcher, our target!
It's not going to be like this forever, is it?
Once we kill them,
we're getting the hell outta here!
Let's go!
All according to plan.
Gunshots from behind?!
That's my—
Come.
I'm going to end this with my next strike.
Look at her, charging like some idiot.
You stupid old man...
What happened to Mama's battle?
It's finally over... I'm so tired.
Mama is victorious! It's all thanks to Anya!
I need to let Olka and the others out.
He successfully disarmed it!
Well done!
It was nothing.
I'm far more nervous about
being surrounded by so many
State Security Service
officers than the bomb.
What's the matter?
Farewell, Princess Lorelei.
Let me hear all the screams of
agony as you sink to your doom.
But I wonder why my weapon was there.
Is there someone else around?
Oh, no! I must withdraw!
The wind must've blown it over.
Director! Are you all right?
There are still multiple bombs?!
If the suspect's goal is to sink this ship,
the amount of gunpowder here
is nowhere near enough.
Just in case, we should
evacuate the guests.
To where, exactly?!
We don't even know how many bombs
there are or where they are.
Besides, the guest list is full
of tons of important people.
We can't cause a commotion!
Must be more State Security
Service officers.
You know what'll happen if
you blab any of this, don't you?
Have anyone who's free right now
check the rest of the ship.
That goes for the crew, too.
Don't let the higher-ups figure
out what you're doing!
I need to hurry back or the lady from
the kids' room is gonna yell at me.
Damn it. This hurts!
I need to extract the bullet.
I can't go with an orthodox
method... I need to regroup.
I'll kill them, no matter what.
A bad guy!
What'd you say, brat?
This scent is...
Gunpowder?!
There's a bomb inside the clock?
There are lots more than the
one Papa's looking for!
Could it be that bastard?
Tch.
Oh, no! I need to let Papa know!
But now I don't know where Papa is!
Actually, I can't tell him, 'cause then
he'd find out about other stuff!
This is bad... There are bombs on the ship!
I know they told me to thoroughly
search the lower decks,
but where do I even start?!
Pardon me.
Huh? What is it, little girl?
Earlier, some old guy I don't know stuck a...
stuck a boogie onto that clock.
That's real gross, so please clean it.
A booger? Sorry, little girl, but I'm busy.
Shock!
Wait... Getting information
about some weirdo right now...
I mean, it's not very likely,
but maybe it couldn't hurt to check...
Okay, I'll take a look.
Seriously...
Those fireworks were amazing, weren't they?
Pardon me, sir.
Tomorrow, we'll be on the island...
Hm, they're coming in loud and clear.
Don't push yourself too much, Director.
Looks like all the assassins
perished up there.
Hey there, Mister Informant.
Where do you think you're
going all by your lonesome?
So you're still alive.
You're the one who planted
the bombs, aren't you?
You were planning to take
all of us out with them?
Quit whining, you loser.
This is the perfect opportunity to send the
targets and the Garden to a watery grave.
I told you some of the client's
guests were on that ship, too!
Like any of them are that important.
Don't worry. The bombs are made to
look like they were made in the West.
If things go well, war will break out again,
and weapon sales will be through the roof.
The client will be plenty happy.
Whatever.
Get this boat moving. I need to regroup.
Who the hell said I'd give you a ride?
There's only enough food
and water for one on board.
In that case... it sounds
like they belong to me.
Bombs have been located
in the third cargo room,
the upper part of the balance tank,
and the boiler room.
Right... I see.
From what you're describing, it sounds like
all the bombs were
planted by the same person.
Please be careful of the trap
I mentioned and proceed with caution.
Okay, on to the next one.
Huh?!
The upper floors... on the eighth deck, too?!
Here it is.
With all these people around?
Their goal isn't just to sink the ship?
We're just doing some
maintenance on the clock here.
We need to get these people away—
No. There's probably no time for that.
What should I do?!
We're just conducting some inspections!
Uh, hello?!
I'm going to go throw this into the ocean!
What?!
I'll let you in on a little
secret before you die.
The second fireworks show is
going to begin any minute now.
You'll be able to enjoy
the symphony of agonized
screams and roars coming through
the wiretaps throughout the ship.
Hey! Wait! That clock is an antique!
Whew, that was close.
Hm? Was there something down there?
What was that noise?
More fireworks?
Could you make some kind of
announcement so there's no commotion?
Understood...
Yay!
He stopped the bombs! All thanks to me!
I found you!
How dare you wander off like that?!
L-Lady! Um...
I-It's because I was about
to poop my pants...
Then you should've just said so!
We're heading back!
Wait! There's still more bombs!
What? You haven't finished pooping yet?
Okay, then we're heading to the bathroom!
Thoroughly inspect each section,
including the upper floors.
It's possible there are still
terrorists on board.
Please request that the State Security
Service be on guard around the clock.
Y-Yes, sir!
I thought I just heard some faint explosions.
Some of them may still remain.
Stay on your guard.
All right. We're all set.
It's a bit early, but let's lower the boat.
Until the cruise ship gets far enough,
please stay covered with this cloth.
All right.
Please continue to take care of yourselves!
Thank you... so much.
U-Um... Your clothes will
get dirty! There's blood—
He wants a hug goodbye, too.
Oh, no! Really! My hands
are all sticky, and...
Your hands... are what
connected him to his future.
He's... so warm.
It might not be something
you can wish for...
I might be overstepping my
bounds... But even so...
I pray that, someday, you and your family
will be able to find true peace.
It looks like there are no problems.
Now we just have to wait for
word from the retrieval ship.
Do not let your guard down
until the dawn breaks—
Don't let yourself actually
become sentimental.
Don't forget that we are nothing
more than foot soldiers.
I... I'm sorry!
By the way...
I forgot I had a message for you.
Forger is trying to set up somewhere
to meet with you tomorrow
on the island we'll be staying at.
Loid and Miss Anya?
Oh, but—
I'll be on the lookout for any stragglers.
As a reward for completing this
mission, see their request through.
Make sure you ice your face so
they don't see the swelling.
And...
Make sure they don't see
the wound on your chest.
I-I won't let them see it!
I won't be wearing a swimsuit!
I was somehow able to
ensure everyone's safety.
I'm sure I can leave the rest
to the State Security Service.
Sorry I'm so late.
I guess she got tuckered out from waiting.
Sorry...
I know it was an emergency, but I ended
up casting my family aside again.
What are you even saying, Twilight?
Your "family" is just another mission.
But no... This time,
my mission was this vacation.
No, wait, it's not a mission... uh...
The bright crimson that
appears right before my eyes
Stretches approximately 40,000 kilometers
Our wounds that inch closer behind us
Make us wander even more
when we're already lost
The unseeable, scentless, unmistakable future
Stabbed me in the back!
So...
Let me stay by your side tonight
Just for tonight, I'm going to be serious
Come closer to me
Even the future we prayed for
Has a different path
My dear
Our malice for each other
Might just get to us
Or maybe not
Enjoy the Resort to the Fullest
Bragging About Vacation